00:03:13,500
苏珊·斯沃茨亚伦的母亲
00:03:14,839
He always accomplished what he wanted.
他总能做成他所想要的事
00:03:18,294
His curiosity was endless.
他总是充满好奇心
00:03:21,158
Here's a little picture of what the planets are.
这张图上画有行星
00:03:25,049
And each planet has a symbol.
每个行星都有个符号
00:03:26,965
Mercury symbol, Venus symbol, Earth symbol, Mars symbol...
水星的符号 金星的符号 地球的符号 火星的符号
00:03:32,970
One day he said to Susan:
有一天他对苏珊说
00:03:34,481
what's this free family entertainment downtown Highland Park?
海兰帕克镇中心的免费家庭娱乐是什么?
00:03:37,283
what's this free family entertainment downtown Highland Park?
海兰帕克镇中心的免费家庭娱乐是什么?
00:03:40,457
He was three at the time.
他那时才三岁
00:03:42,771
And she said: what are you talking about?
所以她问道 你在说什么
