00:02:48,910
Yeah, like a pyramid scheme!
就像金字塔骗局一样
00:02:50,380
Don't think of it so much as a pyramid scheme as a pyramid team.
别这么想 把这想象成金字塔团队
00:02:54,250
You don't even know the best part.
你甚至不知道最好的部分
00:02:55,910
This is the only Donut-Holer
这是唯一一台
00:02:57,620
certified by my close, personal... acquaintance, the Conductor.
由我亲密朋友 售票员认证的甜甜圈机
00:03:02,640
Conductor?!
售票员
00:03:07,860
I'm supposed to be going to Oshkosh.
我本来要去奥什科什
00:03:09,510
It's this place in Wisconsin.
威斯康星的一个地方
00:03:10,660
And, also, my name is Tulip. I should've said that earlier.
而且我的名字是郁金香 我应该早点说的
00:03:13,270
But there's a game-design camp,
但是有一个游戏设计营
00:03:14,380
and my parents signed a contract,
我父母签了合同
