00:18:10,210
You told us to get rid of the clothes.
你让我们把衣服处理掉
00:18:11,720
Oh we got rid of 'em, all right. They're never coming back.
我们照做了 它们再也不会回来了
00:18:16,580
You two are impossible. Why did you even call me here?
你们两个简直绝了 到底为什么要叫我过来
00:18:19,590
Because you're Princess Carolyn, you can fix anything.
因为你是卡洛琳公主 你什么都能处理
00:18:22,010
That's true. But you can't start a fire on your lawn.
这倒是 但是你们不能在自家草坪上点火啊
00:18:25,010
There's a drought and-- There's a drought.
现在正是旱季... 旱季
00:18:27,880
You, thoughtful husband that you are, got rid of your lawn,
你作为一位细心的丈夫 处理掉了草坪
00:18:31,570
and replaced it with drought-resistant landscaping.
换成了抗旱的绿化植被
00:18:34,860
This could work. I got to make a few phone calls.
这个办法能行 我得打几个电话
00:18:37,170
Thanks. You're the best.
谢谢 你最棒了
00:18:38,710
I tell you, I've got half a mind to go over
我跟你说 我得想想办法
