00:14:48,460
I'm all for God,
我相信上帝
00:14:49,580
but contacting the dead is a superstition too far.
但和死人交流就太迷信了
00:14:52,360
Oh, I... I... I don't like the term "dead".
我... 我不喜欢"死人"这个词
00:14:56,800
You're usually so sceptical, Aunt.
你总是持怀疑态度的啊 姨妈
00:14:59,080
Well, as I get older and closer to my...
因为我越来越老 离我的...
00:15:02,380
Departure.
离开
00:15:04,680
Departure... I become more open-minded.
离开越来越近... 我变得开明了很多
00:15:09,360
I'll also cure Margo's spots, using my faith healing.
我也会治好马戈的青春痘 用我的信念疗法
00:15:13,710
I'm afraid I must resume my work.
恐怕我得继续工作了
00:15:15,920
I'm giving a paper about
我在写一篇论文
00:15:17,520
cephalopods and their inky sacs.
是关于头足类动物和它们的墨囊
