01:19:06,310
Clear out the people from this end...
从这儿撒退人手
01:19:08,480
...because I want to start marching in two hours.
我要在二小时内出发
01:19:15,020
And I warn you, you better clear out everybody.
务必撒退所有人员
01:19:22,630
Clutch.
离合器
01:19:29,530
Brake. Brake.
刹车，刹车
01:19:32,370
Clutch. Clutch!
离合器！离合器！
01:19:38,640
I'm teaching him to drive. Just for the hell of it.
我在教他开车
01:19:41,550
Nothing else to do around here anyhow.
反正闲着也是闲着
01:19:44,180
-Still mooning about the schoolmarm? -Sort of.
-还在想那个老师？ -有点
01:19:47,380
I want to move up to Nioko for a few days so we can do a game count.
我想到上游去清理一下
01:19:50,920
-How will this get us through the jungle? -We strip it down.
-这怎能带我们过丛林？ -把壳剥掉就成了
