00:42:34,870
I've got guards from Max covering for right now,
现在重刑监狱的警卫帮忙应付着
00:42:37,160
but that's just temporary.
但只是暂时的
00:42:38,620
I need quality COs. I need guys with experience.
我需要高质量教导官 我需要有经验的人
00:42:42,060
We could pay a bit more, now that we've got all those beds.
本来能再拨点款 但用来添置床位了
00:42:46,270
Quality COs. How, how, how?
高质量教导官 从哪来 从哪来
00:42:52,090
Veterans.
退伍军人
00:42:54,680
The government gives tax credits to companies that hire vets.
政府对雇佣老兵的公司有税收抵免制度
00:42:58,270
You get more money the longer the vet's been out of work.
老兵此前失业时间越久 你得的钱越多
00:43:00,830
We looked into putting that into play at our offices,
我们办公室招人的时候调查过这事
00:43:03,500
but, you know, veterans...
但你懂的 退伍军人...
00:43:08,650
Right, but if we hire them as guards,
是的 但如果我们雇他们来当警卫
