01:02:43,917
Firstly, you must find
首先，你必须再找一根灌木
01:02:46,179
another shrubbery!
01:02:49,958
Not another shrubbery!
我不想找了！
01:02:52,528
Then you must bring it here beside this shrubbery.
你找到那根灌木后 就把它放到这根灌木上
01:02:56,329
Higher, so you get the two-level effect with a path going down the middle.
这样就排成了两层 在中间要留一条小路
01:02:59,869
A path! A path!
一条小路！
01:03:02,599
Then, when you have found the shrubberies,
找到灌木后
01:03:05,640
you must cut down the mightiest tree in the forest
你还必须砍倒森林里最高大的树
01:03:09,811
with a herring!
工具是一条鲱鱼！
01:03:14,551
-We shall do no such thing. -Please.
- 我们做不了这件事 - 哦，去做吧！
01:03:17,221
Cut down a tree with a herring? It can’t be done.
用一条鲱鱼砍倒一棵树？ 这不可能
