00:40:45,520
No.
不会
00:40:47,130
And the other way around as well.
但同样的 我也不会把你说过的话告诉她
00:40:49,160
Oh, that's better.
那倒还好
00:40:51,960
So I think we should start at four days a week.
我觉得一开始最好每周安排四天
00:40:55,150
Let me go get my date book.
我去拿一下工作安排簿
00:41:26,880
- Where's your film? - What film?
-你的广告胶片呢 -什么胶片
00:41:29,360
That's how you're shaking it?
你打算装疯卖傻吗
00:41:30,530
- I heard it stunk. - We didn't make one.
-我听说很烂 -我们没有拍摄广告
00:41:32,680
- It's too expensive. - Well, then you're out of luck, Donny.
-那玩意儿太贵了 -那你这次可不走运了 小唐
00:41:35,770
'cause I sure wouldn't want to follow what I showed them
在我的精彩展示过后 你单凭口头阐释和图片样板
00:41:37,540
with a speech and a couple of posters.
显然是白费力气 自不量力
