00:04:43,470
why you should be hired permanently to your desk.
你们凭什么可以永久占有那张办公桌
00:04:46,750
Pierpoint is the world's
码头灯塔是
00:04:48,220
preeminent financial services institution.
世界一流金融服务机构
00:04:50,820
We expect you to behave like you have a stake in it.
我们期待你们能与公司风雨同舟
00:04:54,260
Act like an owner. Enrich your clients, enrich us,
像主人一样 使客户富有 使我们富有
00:04:58,570
enrich yourselves.
使你们自己富有
00:04:59,960
So, look at the guy or gal next to you.
看看你们身边的人
00:05:03,350
Really look.
仔细看
00:05:04,700
Do you think you're better than them?
你觉得你比他们强吗
00:05:06,760
Maybe you are.
有可能
00:05:08,150
But half of you won't be here in six months.
但你们中有一半的人六个月后不会在这
