00:30:15,660
亚斯卡斯
00:30:18,450
欢迎来到基廷据点努里斯坦省阿富汗
00:30:21,790
前线救护站
00:30:23,410
I pledge allegiance to your pussy.
我发誓对你的下面忠贞
00:30:26,380
Time's almost up, Griff.
快没时间了 格里芬
00:30:28,020
Specialist.
专家
00:30:31,020
Is that how mama taught you how to wear panties?
你妈妈是这样教你穿内裤的吗
00:30:33,090
Griffin, this is your new commander, captain Yllescas.
格里芬 这是你的新指挥官 亚斯卡斯上尉
00:30:37,190
How are you doing, sir?
你好吗 长官
00:30:40,190
Sir, those were Maria Kirilenko's. The tennis star.
长官 这内裤是网球明星玛丽亚·基里连科的
00:30:41,060
601-900 （实习）silence 托比·凯斯Toby Keith 克里斯·科尔多瓦Chris Cordova 罗伯特·亚斯卡斯Rob Yllescas 库维尔医生dr. courville 格里芬Griffin 拉斯基Laski 拉脱维亚Latvia汤姆森 Thomson 罗德里格斯Rodriguez 布里丁Breeding 梅斯Mace 基廷Keating 卡特Carter 帕丽斯·希尔顿Paris Hilton 加勒高Gallegos 纳赛尔Nasir 阿木尔Urmul 彻罗基族人Cherokee 齐佩瓦族Chippewa拉森Larson 穆罕默德Mohammed 马丁Martin
