00:26:38,260
Yes. I have something to show you.
有样东西我希望你能看一下
00:26:40,300
I left your father working in the library.
我留你父亲自己在图书馆工作
00:26:42,180
He sent me to the map section to fetch an ancient plan of the city.
当时他请我去拿旧都市计划图
00:26:45,350
When I got back to his table, he'd gone, with all his papers,
我回来时发现他跟文件不见了
00:26:48,270
except for that scrap, which I found near his chair.
只剩下这张纸 在他的椅子旁边发现的
00:26:50,850
Roman numerals.
是罗马数字
00:26:52,480
Here is the library.
图书馆到了
00:26:54,610
That doesn't look much like a library.
它看起来一点都不像图书馆
00:26:57,490
Looks like a converted church.
比较像是教堂
00:26:59,530
In this case, it's the literal truth.
一点都没错
00:27:01,700
We are on holy ground.
你们来到了圣地
