00:14:02,920
Well, I am definitely doing that at our wedding.
我肯定要在我们的婚礼上那样做
00:14:05,120
And I'll make more money,
而且我会赚更多钱
00:14:05,950
because I've six feet of pinnable area.
因为我身上别钱的区域有六英尺
00:14:09,350
You're incredible.
你真厉害
00:14:11,300
You know what else we could do?
你知道我们还能做什么吗
00:14:12,590
Corporate sponsors.
企业赞助商
00:14:15,460
"Do you, Bonnie, take Adam to be your husband?"
邦妮 你愿意让亚当成为你的丈夫吗
00:14:17,670
"I sure do, especially after driving here
我愿意 特别是在开着泛士通轮胎
00:14:19,790
on Firestone tires."
来这里以后
00:14:24,660
Honey, our wedding could be a real cash cow.
亲爱的 我们可以用婚礼赚大钱
00:14:30,900
I tell you how moved I was by this beautiful ceremony,
我告诉了你这个美丽的仪式多么令我感动
