00:12:03,350
Well, he wouldn't be the first moody Swede.
他不是第一个喜怒无常的瑞典人
00:12:05,890
You're better off with a Finn.
你和芬兰人在一起会更好
00:12:07,420
Well, there weren't any Finns.
这里又没有芬兰人
00:12:10,420
Anyway, he seems to enjoy being...
不管怎么说 他似乎很享受当一个
00:12:12,450
strong and silent and... well...
强壮 安静 以及...
00:12:14,580
male.
具有男子气概的人
00:12:16,520
- So he's like Mr Darcy, in... - Yes,
- 他就像达西先生... - 我知道
00:12:16,520
《傲慢与偏见》中的傲娇男
00:12:18,570
I know what book Mr Darcy is in!
我知道达西先生是哪本书里的
00:12:20,270
Thank you.
谢谢
00:12:22,050
And for all the failings of English men,
尽管英国男人有诸多缺点
