00:36:26,920
So we hope you enjoy your meals here at Jack Rabbit Slim's
希望各位用餐愉快 谢谢大家
00:36:32,390
Phillip Morris!
谁…要…香…烟?
00:36:40,430
What do you think?
如何?
00:36:42,530
I think it's like a wax museum with a pulse
像活的腊像馆
00:36:45,800
Hi, I'm Buddy What can I get you?
我是巴迪 要点些什么?
00:36:52,740
Let's see Steak, steak, steak
牛排…牛排…
00:36:54,510
Yeah, the Douglas Sirk steak I'll have that
我就点道格拉斯牛排
00:36:58,610
How do you want that cooked? Burnt to a crisp, or bloody as hell?
几分熟?要烤焦还是血淋淋
00:37:01,450
Bloody as hell, and oh, yeah, look at this Vanilla Coke
血淋淋 你看 有香草可乐
00:37:06,780
What about you, Peggy Sue?
你呢 女同学?
00:37:08,950
I'll have the Durwood Kirby burger
我点…汉堡
