00:56:24,310
...and both times they trot out very prominent First Amendment lawyers...
这两次他们都搬出 美国宪法第一修正案的大律师
00:56:28,950
...and argue that, ''When we say something is rated triple-A...
争辩〝当我们说某样产品是3A级时〞
00:56:33,280
...that is merely our 'opinion.' You shouldn't rely on it.''
〝那只是我们的“意见” 你们不应该尽信〞
00:56:37,090
S&P's ratings express our opinion.
标准普尔评比表述我们的意见
00:56:39,420
Our ratings are our opinions. They're opinions.
我们的评比是我们的意见 就是意见而已
00:56:42,890
Opinions. And they are just opinions.
意见就只是意见而已
00:56:45,260
l think we are emphasizing the fact that our ratings are opinions.
我想我们要强调 我们的评比是意见
00:56:50,000
(他们不和我们分享他们的意见)
00:56:52,770
(他们都拒绝接受本片采访)
00:56:56,010
They do not speak to the market value of a security...
它们不代表证券的市场价值
00:56:58,980
...the volatility of its price, or its suitability as an investment.
或其价格波动 或其投资适切性
