00:19:58,020
matching you mentors with your soul mates.
使你的导师与你的灵魂伴侣相匹配
00:20:01,480
Our first mentor is Maria Martinez.
我们的第一位导师是玛丽亚·马丁内斯
00:20:04,450
Maria, come on down.
玛丽亚 下来吧
00:20:06,860
Maria was a rare disease specialist
玛丽亚是一位罕见的疾病专家
00:20:08,950
from the University of Mexico.
来自墨西哥大学
00:20:11,410
I'm cured. I'm cured.
我治好了我治好了
00:20:14,120
She'll be matched with one of my favourites,
她会和我的最爱之一搭配
00:20:16,170
soul number 108,210,121,415.
灵魂编号108 210 121 415
00:20:21,000
Congratulations! Off you go.
恭喜
00:20:24,050
Our next mentor is Bjorn T. Börgensson.
我们的下一位导师是比约恩··伯根森
00:20:30,300
Dr Börgensson is a world-renowned child psychologist
鲍根森博士是世界著名的儿童心理学家
