00:11:17,410
What's in that box?
盒子里有什么
00:11:20,420
It would depend on the island...
那要看小岛的情况来决定...
00:11:21,760
where it is, how big, what's the terrain?
它在哪里 有多大 地形什么样
00:11:24,650
Is there fresh water?
有淡水吗
00:11:25,640
Just say the first thing that comes into your head.
说你脑海中的第一样东西就好
00:11:28,120
A pistol.
一把手枪
00:11:29,590
S.H.I.E.L.D. no longer exists.
神盾局已经不存在了
00:11:31,250
The agency has been labeled a terrorist organization.
机构已经被标为恐怖组织
00:11:33,420
So why are you here?
你为什么还在这里
00:11:38,390
I'm an agent. It's my duty.
我是一名特工 这是我的职责
00:11:43,950
I need you to give that to me again.
我需要你再重复一遍
