00:52:28,610
And it's a great day for moving along.
也是前进的好日子
00:52:32,570
And it's a great day from morning to night.
从早到晚都是好时光
00:52:35,240
And it's a great day for everybody's plight.
这是适合许愿的好日子
00:52:46,420
How are you feeling today, Colonel?
今天觉得怎样 中校
00:52:48,670
Super! Superior!
棒 棒极了
00:52:52,010
Superfluous!
棒得过头了
00:52:54,890
Young Sofie here is working Thanksgiving
苏菲感恩节上班
00:52:57,100
because she's trying to put herself through college.
因为她想要读完大学
00:52:59,390
I told her, "My young friend Charlie's headed for college."
我告诉她你也在上大学
00:53:02,940
- Uh, excuse me. - Where you going?
- 抱歉 - 你去哪里?
00:53:05,650
- I need to use the phone. - What's wrong with the phones in here?
- 我要打个电话 - 这儿的电话有问题吗?
