00:00:17,810
It is a beautiful day in Chicago. Temperatures in the upper 70's.
芝加哥今日天朗气清，气温在七十度以上
00:00:23,360
Right now, 75 at the lakefront, 74 at Midway, 73 at O'Hare.
目前在湖畔的气温是七十五度，中途岛七十三度，奥黑尔七十三度
00:00:30,350
春天不是读书天
00:00:35,040
Tom!
汤姆
00:00:39,510
- What's the matter? - It's Ferris Look at him
- 什么事？ - 是费利，看他的样子
00:00:46,550
Ferris?
费利？
00:00:50,800
He doesn't have a fever, but his stomach hurts and he's seeing spots
他没有发烧，但胃痛又头晕眼花
00:00:54,760
- What's the matter, Ferris? - Papa?
- 费利，你没事吧？ - 爸爸？
00:00:58,870
Feel his hands, they're cold and clammy
摸一下他双手，又冷又湿
00:01:06,270
- I'm fine I'll get up - No!
- 我没事，我要起床 - 不行
00:01:11,010
- I have a test today - No
- 我今天有测验 - 不行
