00:40:34,310
Listen, I'm cutting you slack here, I'm trusting you,
听着，我任由你自行其是，我相信你
00:40:36,870
but out there somewhere, some poor bastard's covered in Semtex
但在外面某处，有个可怜的家伙挂满了塑胶炸药…
00:40:40,520
and he's just waiting for you to solve the puzzle, so just tell me,
等着你解决谜题，所以请告诉我…
00:40:43,640
what are we dealing with?
我们面对的是什么情况？
00:40:47,200
Something new.
一种新情况
00:40:58,550
Connection, connection, connection. There must be a connection.
关联 关联 关联 其中必有关联
00:41:03,100
Carl Powers, killed 20 years ago.
卡尔·鲍尔斯，20年前被杀
00:41:04,640
The bomber knew him, admitted that he knew him.
炸弹客认识他，已经承认认识他
00:41:06,790
The bomber's IPhone was in the stationery from the Czech Republic.
炸弹客的苹果手机放在捷克产的信封里
00:41:09,750
The first hostage from Cornwall, the second from London,
第一个人质是康沃尔的，第二个是伦敦的
00:41:11,620
the third from Yorkshire, judging by her accent.
第三个是约克郡的，从口音判断
